<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[The Slums of Palo Alto]]></title>
  <link href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-12-01T16:09:19-08:00</updated>
  <id>http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Mark Fussell]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kindness: Bunnies]]></title>
    <link href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/kindness-bunnies/"/>
    <updated>2015-12-01T09:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/kindness-bunnies</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div style="float:right">
<img src="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/images/Sopa_08_Bunny_12per.png"  alt="Bunny">
</div>


<p>&hellip;One morning, when maybe going out to fish, I encountered a bunny.  The bunny had not had a good day.  Apparently it argued with a cat or other predator, and although it (or maybe I) convinced that other animal to go away, the other animal had done some serious damage in the process.  A rear leg was not really attached anymore, and blood was coming from many different parts of the bunny.  But the bunny was alive.  It was incredibly cute.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I picked up the bunny, and held it.  I had never had something so small, cute, and cuddly in my hands before.  I so wanted to keep this incredible source of happiness as my pet.  Too have my own little bunny, which I would take care of and it would make me happy.</p>

<p>But the extent of the injuries made it obvious that this was not to be&hellip;.</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_kindle">Read the Kindle</a>, <a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_printbw">B&amp;W Print</a>, or <a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_printfc">Full Color Print Version</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love: Programming]]></title>
    <link href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/love-programming/"/>
    <updated>2015-11-30T09:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/love-programming</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div style="float:right">
<img src="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/images/Sopa_05_Pasadena_12per.png"  alt="Pasadena">
</div>


<p>I am a professional programmer, which means I get paid to read and write software.  Fortunately, I love to read and write software, so I am in the right business.  Programming
is amazingly powerful now that robots, the Internet, and almost everything has some kind of program inside it.  I started programming when programming was simpler, which made it easier for me to learn.  And I
am going to teach you how to program by going back to something similarly simple and even tangible.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>For those who think they should scurry to the next chapter out of fear, please fear not.  At worse I will fail.  I am pretty good at that, but sometimes I don’t.  And for those who think they know the art of programming too well to stay, please don’t scurry away, quite yet, either.  For I am not going to just teach you how to program, I am going to teach you how to program in the only true programming language.  This is not just a great programming language; it is truly what “The Matrix”  is made of.  It is the language of the machines and the only true programming language to those machines.  It is named “Machine Language”.  Sadly, computer people are commonly very rigorous and not very creative about how they name things.</p>

<p>To learn the one true language, you will need some playing cards and a desk or relatively empty space in which to work.</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_kindle">Read the Kindle</a>, <a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_printbw">B&amp;W Print</a>, or <a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_printfc">Full Color Print Version</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Love: Nature]]></title>
    <link href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/love-nature/"/>
    <updated>2015-11-23T09:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/love-nature</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<div style="float:right">
<img src="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/images/Sopa_04_Nature_w12per.png"  alt="Nature">
</div>


<p>Nature has an incredible influence on humans.  Yosemite, the Grand Canyon, Bryce, Tahoe, Muir Woods, and many other natural wonders have heavily influenced my family and me.  They are amazing.  You need to see them.  If you have a chance, put this book down right now and make the reservation.  Then pick it back up: you can bring it with you.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Rebecca and I are especially enchanted by Yosemite.  It is awesome, and its awe changes with the seasons, and with the shape of our family.  Rebecca and I went several times when we were young.  We have sat on the top of the fissures staring down several thousand feet at the beautiful valley floor beneath us.  Today, just thinking about it, makes me shudder.  I don’t think at my current age I could sit there and look down.  Too many images of accidentally “taking a leap” fly through my head.</p>

<p>Rebecca and I have also tried to hike up the mist trail to Nevada falls in the winter, but were ultimately repelled by snow and ice.  And one Spring, our whole family caught giant snowflakes that poured down on us in a freakish April snowstorm.  Yosemite is amazing.  And so are all the other national treasures.  Sometimes politicians do the right thing.</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_kindle">Read the Kindle</a>, <a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_printbw">B&amp;W Print</a>, or <a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/slopa_printfc">Full Color Print Version</a></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Live!  B&amp;W Bug!]]></title>
    <link href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/all-live/"/>
    <updated>2015-11-19T09:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/all-live</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It seems I failed again!  The B&amp;W version was a couple versions old (a nearly final test run) and still had
&ldquo;Not yet finished&rdquo;  sections within it.  If you bought one of these, please  <a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/contact">Contact Me</a> and I will
send you a replacement.  The Color and Kindle versions were fine, but because it takes the book offline, I
didn&rsquo;t want the B&amp;W version to disappear.  I accidentally held off too long and
forgot the B&amp;W needed updating.</p>

<p>Thanks to Jack for letting me know the mistake.  It was fixed today.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kindle Live!]]></title>
    <link href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/kindle-live/"/>
    <updated>2015-11-07T09:00:00-08:00</updated>
    <id>http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/kindle-live</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Well, it has been an extra year in the making, but the final version of &ldquo;The Slums of Palo Alto&rdquo; is now going live on
Amazon in Kindle, B&amp;W, and Color formats.  Thanks to everyone who has helped along the way, and please
<a href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/contact">Let Me Know</a> what you think of the new version.  It has been highly edited: things that were
 off the core topics of the book are now gone, the rest is now fleshed out, and I believe the end is <em>much</em> better.</p>

<ul>
<li> Author Page: <a href="http://www.amazon.com/author/markfussell/">http://www.amazon.com/author/markfussell/</a></li>
<li> The Slums of Palo Alto: How to success through relentless failure

<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.amazon.com/Slums-Palo-Alto-succeed-relentless-ebook/dp/B017PHSSNG/" target="_blank">Kindle, English, Full Color</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.amazon.com/Slums-Palo-Alto-succeed-relentless/dp/1519145284/">Book, English, B&amp;W</a></li>
<li><a href="http://www.amazon.com/Slums-Palo-Alto-succeed-relentless/dp/1519177291/">Book, English, Full Color</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>


<p>At least half the profits for all the books go to educational programs.  See <a href="http://MinimalBuyableBook.com/">MinimalBuyableBook.com</a> for
more information</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Site Launch!]]></title>
    <link href="http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/site-launch/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-21T15:17:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://slumsofpaloalto.github.io/blog/site-launch</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Earlier today I decided that I should have a site for the book.  After doing so many startups, and with some great services out there,
launching the IT (or Infrastructure) of a new company is incredibly easy.  A web site is among the easiest of the infrastructure to
set up.  I purchased the domain name, pointed it at github.io, cloned and customized Octopress, and after a few &lsquo;rake generate; rake deploy&rsquo;
edit cycles, the book proposal and this blog posting were up and alive.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
